Finding Aid to the Women's Project Theater records SSC.MS.00361
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES I. Plays, 1963-2008; 55.333 linear feet (66 containers)
  - Real Life by Susan Yankowitz, draft script, 1993 (Box 40)
  - The Reading by Kathleen Collins, script, 1984-1985 (Box 40)
  - Real Women Have Curves by Josefina Lopez, script, correspondence, reviews, miscellaneous materials, 1988-1993 (Box 41)
  - Reclaimed by Judy GeBauer, script with draft, 1992-1993 (Box 41)
  - The Reincarnation of Jamie Brown by Lynne Alvarez, 1987-1988 (Box 41)
  - Relativity by Marlane Meyer, script, program, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Remote Control by Lynda Sturner, script, flyer, 1995 (Box 41)
  - Remnants by Judith Gilhousen, scripts, 1983 (Box 41)
  - Report to the Academy by Susan Batson and Dorothy Batson Owusu, program flyer, 1990-11-08 (Box 41)
  - Rescuing Marilyn by Kate Moira Ryan, draft script, 1989 (Box 41)
  - Reunion by Paula Giddings, script with drafts and Departures program, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Reverend Jenkins' Almost All Colored Orphanage Band, book and lyric by Gail Kriegel, lyrics and music by Luther Henderson, Jabbo Smith; scripts, program, posters, correspondence, contracts, resumes, reviews, miscellaneous materials, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Box 98)
    2 posters, 18"x24", in flat box 98
  - Sound recordings of Reverend Jenkins' Almost All Colored Orphanage Band by Gail Kriegel, 1986-1998; 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 93, Box 94)
  - The Ring by Gail Noppe-Brandon, scripts with notes, 1993 (Box 42)
  - The Ring by Taylor Barton, script, 1999 (Box 42)
  - Rom Com by Phyllis Purscell, script, flyer, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Rosa Loses Her Face by Kitty Chen, partial script, 1989 (Box 42)
  - Rowing to America by Kitty Chen, script, Tandem Acts flyers, 1996 (Box 42)
  - Saadawi by Eliza Watt, script, 1986 (Box 42)
  - A Safe Place by Carol K. Mack, script, correspondence, clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 42)
  - Sound recordings of A Safe Place by Carol K. Mack, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - A Safe Place by Anne Garcia-Romero, script, 1993 (Box 42)
  - St. Joan and the Dancing Sickness by Julie Herbert, script, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1998 (Box 42)
  - St. Lucy's Eyes by Bridgette A. Wimberly, script, study guide, correspondence, publicity, correspondence, reviews, original oversize costume designs, miscellaneous materials, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Box 98)
    Eight 11 1/2"x15 1/4" pencil drawings on costumes, some signed by the designer, in flat Box 98.
  - Sand by Trista Baldwin, study guides, review clipping, 2008 (Box 43)
  - Scene of Shipwreck by Pamela Mills, script, casting lists, notes, correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - A Second Coming by Anne Garcia-Romero, script, 1992-10 (Box 43)
  - Sedalia Run by Katharine Long, script, publicity, 1988 (Box 43)
  - Seduction Duet by Marjorie Appleman, script, 1991 (Box 43)
  - Separate Ceremonies by Phyllis Purscell, script, correspondence, note, miscellaneous materials, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Sound recordings of Separate Ceremonies by Phyllis Purscell, 1979; 4 items (4 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - Shades of Grey by Joan Vail Thorne, script, 2002 (Box 43)
  - Shadows by Michael angel Johnson, script, 1986-1988 (Box 43)
  - The Shawl by Cynthia Ozick, script, 1980-1999 (Box 43)
  - Shelter by Caridad Svich, revised script, 1991-08 (Box 43)
  - She's Not My Relative by Kitty Chen, 1992-1994 (Box 43)
  - She Talks to Beethoven by Adrienne Kennedy, script, 1980-1999 (Box 43)
  - Shot While Dancing by Hillary Bell, script, 2000 (Box 43)
  - Shout: The Mod Musical by Phillip Charles and David Lowenstein, playbill, publicity, cliupping, 1963 (Box 43)
  - Signatures by Karen Gottleib, script, 1982-1983 (Box 43)
  - Signs and Wonders by Joan Vail Throne, 1998 (Box 43)
  - Signs of Life by Joan Schenkar, program, publicity, correspondence, clippings, contracts, miscellaneous materials, 1987-1988 (Box 43)
  - Sound recordings of Signs of Life by Joan Schenkar, 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - Silence of God by Catherine Filloux, script, 2002 (Box 43)
  - Singin' in the Flame by Kia Corthron, script, 1988 (Box 43)
  - Sirens by Stephanie Lehman, scripts, 1998 (Box 43)
  - Sisters Lament by Meredith Muncy, script, 1990 (Box 44)
  - Sound recordings of The Sixth Season by Kathleen Cahill, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 95)
  - A Small Delegation by Janet Neipris, script, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Smudge by Rachel Axler, student study guide, undated (Box 44)
  - Something Deliberate by Jean Vail Thorne, script with notes, 1986 (Box 44)
  - Sound recordings of Something Wonderful by June Siegel, 1992; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 94)
  - Snowstorms by Sophy Burnham, script, clippings, correspondence, miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 44)
  - Song of Lawino, an epic poem by Okot p'Bitek, 1966 (Box 44)
  - A Son of Africa by Hilary Blecher, scripts, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
  - Spare Parts by Elizabeth Page, script, flyer, 1985 (Box 44)
  - Spinning Into the Blue by Sally Nemeth, scripts, notes, 1989-1990 (Box 44)
  - Spyglass by Cindy Cooper, script, 1995-04 (Box 44)
  - Square Blues by Shay Youngblood, script, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Stardust by Elizabeth Gould Hemmerdinger, script, 1991 (Box 44)
  - Stargazers by Chiori Miyagawa, scrript, 2002 (Box 44)
  - States of Independence text by Tina Landau, music by Ricky Ian Gordon, script, budget, press clippings, contracts, miscellaneous materials, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Stealing Fire by Diana Son, script, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Stigmata and Other Symptoms by Kate Robin, script, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Still Life by Emily Mann, script, program, press clippings, contracts, miscellaneous materials, 1980-1981 (Box 45)
  - Sound recording of Still Life?, 3 items (Three audio reel-to-reel tapes) (Box 97)
  - Stolen Goods by Diane Kagan, script, 1986 (Box 45)
  - Strange Case of Mary Lincoln by June Bingham, program, clippings, correspondence, notes, 2001 (Box 45)
  - Sound recording of The Strange Case of Mary Lincoln demo, 1 items (One CD) (Box 97)
  - Strange Kindness by Brooke Berman, script, 2000 (Box 45)
  - Strollin' by Eliza Wyatt, script, 1992 (Box 45)
  - The Study by Sophie Bunham, scripts, 1979-1987 (Box 45)
  - Suffering Heart Salon by Rosemarie Caruso, script, 1983 (Box 45)
  - The Summer at Gossensass by Marie Irene Fornes, drafts and final scripts, notes, production, research and miscellaneous materials, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Box 46, Box 47)
  - Sound recordings of Summer in Gossensass by Maria Irene Fornes, 1998; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 94)
  - Floppy Disks of Summer in Gossensass final script, 1998; 3 items (Three floppy disks) (Box 97)
  - Susan B. by Lavonne Mueller, script with draft, correspondence, photo slides and miscellaneous materials, 1981 (Box 47)
  - Sound recordings of Susan B. by Lavonne Mueller, 1981; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 94)
  - S.W.A.K. by Sally Ordway, program, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1979-1980 (Box 47)
  - Sound recordings of S.W.A.K. by Sally Ordway, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - Swan by Elizabeth Egloff, scripts, 1990 (Box 47)
  - Sweater Something by Ruth Margaff, script, production schedule and miscellaneous materials, 1992 (Box 47)
  - Sweet Mary Divine by Patricia Langford, scripts, notes, correspondence and miscellaneous materials, 1991-1992 (Box 47)
  - Taking Our Place in Time by Clare Coss, script, contact sheet, 1999 (Box 47)
  - Tales of the Last Formicans by Constance Congdon, revised script, publicity, budgets, reviews, correspondence, program, contracts and miscellaneous materials, 1988-1990 (Box 47)
  - Talking Turkey by Carol Thompson Hemingway, script, 1983-1984 (Box 48)
  - Tangents by Elizabeth Hansen, scripts, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1997 (Box 48)
  - Taproom by Karen Jones-Meadows, scripts, 1983-1987 (Box 48)
  - Tarpon Springs by Stephanie Cotsirilos, scripts with notes, 1986-1988 (Box 48)
  - Sound recordings of Tarpon Springs by Stephanie Cotsirilos, cues, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 94)
  - A Taste of the Tropics by Nancy F. Lubet, script, 1980-1999 (Box 48)
  - Terms by Joan Vail Thorne, script, 1979-1980 (Box 48)
  - Terra Incognito script and libretto by Maria Irene Forness, script, music, production information, and miscellaneous materials, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Box 49)
  - Sound recordings of Terra Incognita by Maria Irene Forness, 1996-1997; 6 items (6 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - Territorial Rites by Carol K. Mack, scripts, production materials, notes, contracts, programs, miscellaneous materials, 1982 (Box 49)
  - Sound recording of Territorial Rites sound cues, 1 items (One audio reel-to-reel tape) (Box 97)
  - Testimony by Rigoberta Menchu, scripts, 1985-1986 (Box 49)
  - Testing by Lucy Tom Lehrer, script, flyer (Box 49)
  - That Soft and Gentle Cushion by Kitty Chen, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Them That's Got by Robyn Hatcher, scripts, 1988-1989 (Box 49)
  - Thin Air: Tales From a Revolution by Lynne Alvarez, scripts, 1988-1990 (Box 49)
  - Thirty-Nine Seconds and Counting by Marjorie Applebaum, 1984-1985 (Box 49)
  - Sound recordings of This Heart of Mine by Barbara Carroll, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 94)
  - This is Ecstasy Talking by Susan Brownmiller, script, 1990-10 (Box 49)
  - Those Sweet Carresses by Lucy Tom Lehrer, script with drafts, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1990-1994 (Box 49)
  - Throwaway by Sallie Bingham, scripts with contact sheet, 1988-2001 (Box 49)
  - Together in the Night by Anne Garcia-Romero, script, 1989-12 (Box 49)
  - To Heaven in a Swing by Katherine Houghton, program, correspondence, photograph, production and miscellaneous materials, 1983-1984 (Box 50)
  - Tom, Dick and Harry by Sharon Tipsworld, script, pencil drawing, audience list, miscellaneous materials, 1978-1983 (Box 50)
  - Sound recordings of Tom, Dick and Harry by Sharon Tipsworld, 1978; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - Tomorrowland by Neena Beber, scripts, programs, 1995 (Box 50)
  - Tone Clusters by Joyce Carol Oates, scripts, flyer, 1990-1991 (Box 50)
  - The Totem Meal by France Burke, 1984 (Box 50)
  - Topographical Eden by Brighde Mullins, script, 1997 (Box 50)
  - Touch by Toni Press-Coffman, script, clippings, budget, program, miscellaneous materials, 2002-2003 (Box 50)
  - Transfigures by Lear DeBessonet, clippings, 2007 (Box 50)
  - Translators by Sally Ordway, script, 1985 (Box 50)
  - Trapped Daylight by Sharon Houck Ross, script, 1992 (Box 50)
  - Trayf by Lucy Wang, script, 1994 (Box 50)
  - Treason by Sallie Bingham, scripts, 2002 (Box 50)
  - the trial and conviction of susie q by Rachel Sheinkin, script, 1980-1999 (Box 50)
  - Tsunami by Christina de Lancie, script, 1999 (Box 50)
  - Twenty-four Hours in the Life of the Belted Sandfish, by Cynthia L. Cooper, scripts, 1991 (Box 50)
  - Twister by Margie Duffield, script, 1995 (Box 50)
  - Two-Headed by Julie Jensen, scripts, programs, correspondence, notes, blueprints and miscellaneous materials, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Box 51)
  - Under the Skin by Susan Yankowitz, scripts, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1994-1995 (Box 51)
  - The Universal Wolf by Joan M. Schenkar, script, publicity cards, 1996 (Box 52)
  - The Vada Plays, a trilogy of one-act plays by Joan Vail Thorne, scripts, 1988-1989 (Box 52)
  - Variations in Ursa Major by Carol k. Mack, scripts, 1993-1994 (Box 52)
  - Victoria Martin: Math Team Queen by Kathryn Walat, clippings, publicity, 2007 (Box 52)
  - Sound recording of Violent Peace, 1 items (One audio reel-to-reel tape) (Box 97)
  - Visitation by J.L. Floyd, 1992 (Box 52)
  - The Waiting Room by Lisa Loomer, script, 1994 (Box 53)
  - Wake Up Lou by Kia Corthron, script, 1990 (Box 53)
  - The Wall Between by Sallie Bingham, scripts, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1982-1987 (Box 53)
  - Sound recordings of The Wall Between by Sallie Bingham, 1982; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 94)
  - Warriors From a Long Childhood Lavonne Mueller, scripts, programs, tickets sales reports, contracts, miscellaneous materials, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
  - Sound recordings of Warriors from a Long Childhood by Lavonne Mueller, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - The Water Children by Wendy MacLeod, scripts, programs, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1977 (Box 53)
  - Watermelon Rinds by Regina Taylor, scripts, flyers, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1990-1993 (Box 53)
  - The Water Principal by Eliza Anderson, 1989-1991 (Box 53)
  - We Agree! We Agree! by Pamela Mills, script, notes, 1988-1994 (Box 54)
  - Sound recordings of Weaving by Doris Hays, 1984; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 94)
  - A Weekend Near Madison by Kathleen Tolan, script, 1979-1982 (Box 54)
  - Sound recordings of A Weekend Near Madison by Kathleen Tolan, 1982; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - Weldon Rising by Phyllis Nagy, script, 1991 (Box 54)
  - When I Wake Up to Sleep No More by Mary Sue Price, script, 1991 (Box 54)
  - When I Was a Girl I used to Scream and Shout by Sharman MacDonald, script, notes, Playbill, articles, 1991-1992 (Box 54)
  - Where Are We Going, Where Have We Been? Symposium, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Where the Wind Begins by Marjorie Appleman, script, 1991 (Box 54)
  - While Older Men Speak by Kathleen Collins, script, 1985 (Box 54)
  - The White Album by Laura Quinn, scripts, 1991 (Box 54)
  - White River by Mary Sue Price, scripts, 1989-1992 (Box 54)
  - Why We Have a Body by Claire Chafee, scripts, Showbill, news clippings, publicity, contracts, box office report, contact list, 1993-1999 (Box 54)
  - Widows Walk by Susan Flakes, script, 1982 (Box 54)
  - Winding the Ball by Alex Finlayson, workshop script, 1987-1988 (Box 54)
  - Winterplay by Adele Edling Shank, script and rehearsed reading notes, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Sound recordings of Winterplay by Adele Edling Shank, 1980; 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 94)
  - Woman in Chain by Laura Quinn, rehearsed reading script, publicity, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Woman Get Up by Sallie Bingham, script (Box 55)
  - The Woman Who Laughed by Joyce Carol Oates, scripts, 1994 (Box 55)
  - The Women of Lockerbie by Deborah Brevoort, contact sheet, publicity, photo, legal agreements, budgets, contracts and grant certificate, 1998-2003 (Box 55)
  - Women's Work publicity, 2005-2006 (Box 55)
  - Sound recordings of Women Who Cook: Soviet Peace Tour by unknown author, 1989; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 94)
  - Women with the Mind of Winter by Lavonne Mueller, scripts, 1993-1994 (Box 55)
  - Wonderful Women, Wonderful Town event, 2004 (Box 55)
  - The Worgelt Study by Kate Moira Ryan, script, 1996 (Box 55)
  - A Working Breakfast by Lavonne Mueller, readings script, 1984-1985 (Box 55)
  - The Wreck of the Hesperus by Patty Lynch, script, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Years by Honor Moore, scripts and readings material, 1978 (Box 55)
  - Sound recordings of Years by Honor Moore, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 95)
  - Yellow Ray Flowers (Bodyworks) by Ellen Gilchrist, readings script, 1985 (Box 55)
  - Sound recordings of The Yellow Wallpaper by Ronald Perera, 1992; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 95)
  - The Yiddish Trojan Women by Carole Braverman, script, 1990-1993 (Box 55)
  - Yonnondio from the Thirties by Tillie Olsen, script, 1980-1999 (Box 55)
  - You Can't Always Get What You Want by Paula Cizmar, script, 1985 (Box 55)
  - You Could Be Home Now by Ann Magnuson, script, Playbill, designers, contact sheet, correspondence, resumes, marketing, press clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 56)
  - You Gotta Have Heart (Untitled) by Laura Maria Censabella, script, 1990 (Box 56)
  - Your Mom's a Man by Alice Know, script, 1988 (Box 56)
  - You Strike the Woman You Strike the Rock by Vusisizwe Players, publicity, 1988 (Box 56)
  - Unidentified page of a script, 1970-1989 (Box 56)
- SERIES II. Administrative Files, 1972-2010; 29.042 linear feet (34 containers)
  Series II includes materials from the the administration files of WP Theater. These records include newsletters, budgets and financial materials, correspondence, board minutes, education program materials, information on festivals and series, and logs and evaluations of scripts submitted to WP theater. The publicity materials include art work, such as oversize posters and graphic artist's boards. Records are arranged alphabetically.
  - Administrative Files, General, 1991-2008 (Box 57)
  - 365 Plays Festival, 2007 (Box 57)
  - American Express, 1985-1989 (Box 57)
  - America Place Theater, 1978-1987 (Box 57)
  - Anthology, General, 1979-2003 (Box 57)
  - Anthology, The Great Monologues of the Women's Project, 1994 (Box 57)
  - Anthology, Here to Stay, 1997 (Box 57)
  - Anthology, Out of Time and Place, 2010 (Box 57)
  - Anthology, Playwrighting Women, 1993 (Box 57)
  - Anthology, Signs of Life, 1998 (Box 58)
  - Anthology, A Theater for Women's Voices, 2003 (Box 58)
  - Anthology, Women Heroes, 1987 (Box 58)
  - Anthology, Women's Project and Productions, 2002 (Box 58)
  - Anthology, The Women's Project, 1980 (Box 58)
  - Anthology, The Women's Project 2, 1984 (Box 58)
  - Anthology, Womenswork, 1989 (Box 58)
  - Antigone Project, 2004 (Box 58)
  - Awards, Bellagio Award, 1982-1988 (Box 58)
  - Awards, Susan B. Anthony Award, 1989-1990 (Box 58)
  - Awards, Susan Smith Blackburn Prize, 1981-1990 (Box 58)
  - Benefits, 1980-1999 (Box 58)
  - Board, 1983-1991 (Box 58)
  - Body Politic, 2004 (Box 58)
  - Bodyworks, 1984-1985 (Box 58)
  - Choices, 1978-1979 (Box 58)
  - Clippings, 1985-2001 (Box 59)
  - College of Insurance, 1987-1988 (Box 59)
  - Composers, General, 1992-1995 (Box 59)
  - Composers, George Broderick, 1987 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Mark Bruckner, 1998 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Cindy Bullens, 2001-2003 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Sande Campbell, 1993 (Box 59)
  - Composers, John Domke, 1990 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Linda Dowdell, 1993-1998 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Ian Gordon, 1999 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Lara Grete, 1990 (Box 59)
  - Sound recordings of music by Gina Leishman, composer, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 95)
  - Composers, Wynton Marsalis, 2001 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Carmel Owen, 2003 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Kim Sherman, 1988-2001 (Box 59)
  - Composers, Adrienne Torf, 1985-1994 (Box 59)
  - Conferences, 1993-1997 (Box 59)
  - Conferences, Women in Theater, 1997 (Box 59)
  - Departures, 1990-1991 (Box 59)
  - Development, 1992-1994 (Box 59)
  - Difficult Women Project, 1983-1985 (Box 59)
  - Video recording of Directing Program, 1983-1984; 2 items (Two VHS cassette tapes) (Box 97)
  - Directors, Josephine Abady, 1982-2002 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Joanne Akalaitis, 1990-1993 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Billie Allen, 1976-2002 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Marcella Andre, 1986-1999 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Cecilia Antionette, 2000 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Marcy Arlin, 1994-1999 (Box 59)
  - Diectors, Mary Arlin, 1991-1993 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Peter Askin, 2001 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Jane Atkinson, 1997 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Linda Atkinson, 1992 (Box 59)
  - Directors, "Beth B", 1999 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Kate Baggot, 1993 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Vernal Bagnersis (Box 59)
  - Directors, Lisa Barnes, 1993 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Jessica Bauman, 1994 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Alma Becker, 1986-1991 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Elaine Bennet, 1982 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Suzanne Bennett, 1990-2001 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Melia Bensussen, 1990-1998 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Jackie Berger, 1993 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Pamela Berlin, 1987-1999 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Patricia Birch, 1999 (Box 59)
  - Directors, Hilary Blecher, 1988-1998 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Anne Bogart, 1988-1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Jo Bonney, 1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Robin Bower, 1992 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Julianne Boyd, 1984-2003 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Veronica Brady, 1988 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Yanna Brandt, 1990-2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Margot Brier, 1993-1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Susann Brinkley, 1985-1995 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Mirra Brockman, 1995-1997 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Rebecca Brown, 2001 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Mark Brokaw, 1996 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Page Burkholder, 1989 (Box 60)
  - Directors, William Carden, 1998 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Patricia Carmichael, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Kay Carney, 1982-1990 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Juliette Carrillo, 1994-1997 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Joseph Chaiken, 1991 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Leonora Champagne, 1993-1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Tisa Chang, 1980-1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Linda Chapman, 1981-1992 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Tina Chen, 1993-1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Eranne Christian, 1981-1994 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Nancy Chu, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Marya Cohn, 1990-2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Michele Coleman, 1992 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Beatriz Cordoba, 1993-1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Lee Costello, 1989-1991 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Geraldine Court, 1978-1979 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Mark Wing Davies, 2002 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Lenore Dekoven, 1984-1986 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Heather de Michael (Box 60)
  - Directors, Margaret Denithorne, 1979 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Liza Diamond, 1989-2003 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Melanie Doreth, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Toni Dorfman, 1990-1994 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Olympia Dukakis, 1987 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Anne D'Zumura, 1993 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Mary Beth Easley, 1992-2007 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Lydia Ecker, 1981 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Gordon Edelstein, 1982-1990 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Susan Einhorn, 1980-2001 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Andre Ernotte, 1990 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Nuria Espert (Box 60)
  - Directors, Jim Farmer, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Max Ferra, 2003 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Evadne Giannini, 1982 (Box 60)
  - Directors, April Dawn Gladu, 1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Jennifer Uphoff Gray, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Monika Gross, 1999-2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Wendy Goldberg, 1993 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Andra Gordon, 1980 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Denise Gordon, 1997-2001 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Loretta Greco, 1989 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Sydnie Grosberg, 1991 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Mark Harboith, 1989-1990 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Rosemary Hay, 1990 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Terese Hayden, 1978 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Esther Herbst, 1980 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Gitta Honegger, 1979 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Bette Howard (Box 60)
  - Directors, Imani, 1986-1988 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Vincent Irving, 1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Meachie Jones, 1989-1990 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Ernestine Johnson, 1980-1981 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Melanie Joseph, 1995-1998 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Sheryl Kaller, 2003 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Anne Kauffman, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Caroline Kava, 1983-1999 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Sonoko Kawahara, 2000-2001 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Rosa Allen Kazlas (Box 60)
  - Directors, Susan Kerner (Box 60)
  - Directors, Anite Khanzadian, 1975-1979 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Rachel Kranz, 1993 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Kevin Kuhlke, 1991 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Kati Kuroda, 1995 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Tina Landau, 1991-1993 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Mahayana Landowne, 2000 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Sue Lawless, 1978-1993 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Wendi Lazar, 1988 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Susan Leaming, 1982 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Sondra Lee (Box 60)
  - Directors, Susan Lehmen, 1978-1979 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Irene Lewis, 1993 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Roberta Levitow, 1987-1991 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Mama Lion, 1993-1994 (Box 60)
  - Directors, Greg Lombardo, 1998 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Kay Long, 1995-1998 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Karen Ludwig, 1985 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Elizabeth Margid, 1997 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Charles Maryan, 2000 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Marya Mazor, 2002 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Liz McDonald, 1997 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Vijaya Mehta, 1995-2002 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Kate Mennone, 1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Maria Mileaf, 1995-2000 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Lou Na Ming (Box 61)
  - Directors, Alison Narver, 2001 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Gloria Muzio, 1991-1999 (Box 61)